<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Good Morning</string>
    <string name="tick">\u2713</string>
    <string name="createAlarm">Create Alarm</string>
    <string name="alarms">Alarms</string>
    <string name="alarmicon">alarmIcon</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="okay">OKAY</string>
    <string name="weather_dialog_title">Enable Search</string>
    <string name="weather_dialog_message">Do you want to enable location search.</string>
    <string name="weather_dialog_title_toinvisible">Disable Search</string>
    <string name="weather_dialog_message_toinvisible">Do you want to disable location search.</string>
    <string name="next">NEXT</string>
    <string name="previous">PREVIOUS</string>
    <string name="login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="email">Email *</string>
    <string name="phonenumber">Phone Number *</string>
    <string name="country">Country *</string>
    <string name="password">Password *</string>
    <string name="register">Create Account</string>
    <string name="dark_theme">Dark Theme</string>
    <string name="dark_theme_request">Which theme you want to use?</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="light">Light</string>
    <string name="dark">Dark</string>
    <string name="info">Tell us something about you.</string>
    <string name="firstname">First Name *</string>
    <string name="lastname">Last Name *</string>
    <string name="image_upload_title">Uploading profile photo</string>
    <string name="image_upload_message">Hold on just uploading your picture</string>
    <string name="typeOfSleeper">Could you tell us what type of sleeper are you? So that we can recommend you an alarm.</string>
    <string name="proAtSleep">I am pro at sleep</string>
    <string name="wakeUpAtTimeRarely">I rarely wake up on time.</string>
    <string name="wakeUpAtTimeOften">I often wake up on time.</string>
    <string name="voiceSettings">Do you want voice settings?</string>
    <string name="voiceForBoth">I want voice for everything.</string>
    <string name="onlyWeather">I want voice only for weather.</string>
    <string name="login_screen">Hey, welcome back!</string>
    <string name="noVoice">I don\'t want voice settings.</string>
    <string name="noAccount">Don\'t have an account yet?\n\t\t\t\tCreate one here.</string>
    <string name="permission">Permission Request</string>
    <string name="permission_message">Kindly give us these permissions.</string>
    <string name="display_over_other_apps">Display Over Other Apps permission required for Android Version > 9</string>
    <string name="settingsHeading">Settings</string>
    <string name="profileHeading">My Profile</string>
    <string name="defaultVal">Default</string>
    <string name="alarm_clock">Alarm Clock</string>
    <string name="alarm_clock_old">Alarm Clock Old</string>
    <string name="off">Off</string>
    <string name="beeps">Beeps</string>
    <string name="siren">Siren</string>
    <string name="tuning">Tuning</string>
    <string name="gi1">Gradually Increasing 1</string>
    <string name="gi2">Gradually Increasing 2</string>
    <string name="gi3">Gradually Increasing 3</string>
    <string name="gi4">Gradually Increasing 4</string>
    <string name="gi5">Gradually Increasing 5</string>
    <string name="gi6">Gradually Increasing 6</string>
    <string name="la1">Loud Alarm 1</string>
    <string name="la2">Loud Alarm 2</string>
    <string name="la3">Loud Alarm 3</string>
    <string name="la4">Loud Alarm 4</string>
    <string name="la5">Loud Alarm 5</string>
    <string name="la6">Loud Alarm 6</string>
    <string name="la7">Loud Alarm 7</string>
    <string name="la8">Loud Alarm 8</string>
    <string name="la9">Loud Alarm 9</string>
    <string name="nil">Nil</string>
    <string name="snooze">SNOOZE</string>
    <string name="everyday">Everyday</string>
    <string name="weekdays">Weekdays</string>
    <string name="dataUnavailable">Sorry your account is not created properly, please write us at support@zerostic.com</string>
    <string name="dataUnavailableTitle">Account Error</string>
    <string name="tos">I agree to all the Terms of Zerostic</string>
    <string name="payments">Payments</string>
    <string name="paymenticon">payment icon</string>
    <string name="plans_offered">We offer two plans for subscription.</string>
    <string name="pay">Pay</string>
    <string name="rsplan1">\u20B9 11.99/month</string>
    <string name="rsplan2">\u20B9 119.90/year</string>
    <string name="usdplan1">$ 0.50/3 months</string>
    <string name="usdplan2">$ 1.64/year</string>
    <string name="select_difficulty_level">Select difficulty level</string>
    <string name="shake_intensity">Shake intensity</string>
    <string name="shake_count">How many times do you want to shake your device</string>
    <string name="add_code">Add A Bar Code</string>
    <string name="numOfSteps">Number of steps</string>
    <string name="patternType">Select a pattern type</string>
    <string name="napping">Napping</string>
    <string name="resetPassword">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="missing_data">Information Missing</string>
    <string name="confirmation">Confirmation</string>
    <string name="logout">Once you verify yourself you need to login again.</string>
    <string name="verifiedUser">Verified User</string>
    <string name="goodnight">Good Night</string>
    <string name="start">START</string>
    <string name="information">Information</string>
    <string name="trackerStart">Your tracker will start automatically in 7 minutes… \nSweet Dreams!!!</string>
    <string name="stop">STOP</string>
    <string name="trackerStarted">Tracker Started</string>
    <string name="trackerStop">Alright! I\'ll stop the timer.</string>
    <string name="deepsleep">Deep Sleep</string>
    <string name="moderatesleep">Moderate Sleep</string>
    <string name="lightsleep">Light Sleep</string>
    <string name="sleepTime">Sleep Time</string>
    <string name="totalSleepHour">Slept for</string>
    <string name="deleteConfirmation">Are you sure you want to delete Tracker data.</string>
    <string name="swipe"><![CDATA[Swipe >>]]></string>
    <string name="weather">Weather Settings</string>
    <string name="contactus">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="speech">Voice Settings</string>
    <string name="afterEveryAlarm">After every alarm.</string>
    <string name="iWantWeather">I want weather</string>
    <string name="onlyForMorningAlarms">Only for morning alarms.</string>
    <string name="never">Never</string>
    <string name="ZerosticEmail">support@zerostic.com</string>
    <string name="iWantSpeech">I want voice</string>
    <string name="atWakeUpCheck">At Wake Up Check</string>
    <string name="atWeather">At Weather</string>
    <string name="step1">Go to Settings</string>
    <string name="step2">Go to Accessibility</string>
    <string name="step3">Click on Text-to-speech output</string>
    <string name="step4">Click on Install voice data</string>
    <string name="step5">Search for your preferred language, install the voice you like and you are good to go</string>
    <string name="forEveryThing">For everything</string>
    <string name="on">ON</string>
    <string name="Off">OFF</string>
    <string name="recurring">recurring</string>
    <string name="licenses"><u>Licenses</u></string>
    <string name="copyright">\u00a9 Zerostic</string>
    <string name="credits"><u>Credits</u></string>
    <string name="termsncondition">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="privacyPolicy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="Zerosticlogo">ZerosticLogo</string>
    <string name="gmlogo">gmLogo</string>
    <string name="refundPolicy">Refund Policy</string>
    <string name="license">Open Source Libraries</string>
    <string name="credit">Credits To</string>
    <string name="terms">"<b>Terms of Service</b>\n\nWe know it’s boring and its something no one wants to look at, but it’s important what you can expect from us and what we can expect from you as you use our services.\n\n<b>Thank you for choosing Zerostic.</b>\n\nThis is a license agreement between you and Zerostic. This agreement describes your rights and the conditions upon which you may use Zerostic software’s and services. You should review the entire agreement, including any supplemental license terms that accompany the software and any linked terms, because all the terms are important and together create this agreement that applies to you.\n<b>\nBy accepting this agreement or using our software or service, you agree to all these terms, and consent to the transmission of certain information during account creation and during your use of the software or services. If you do not accept and comply with these terms, you may not use the software or its features.</b>\n\n<b>1) Installation and Use Rights</b>\n\nThe software is licensed, not sold. Under this agreement, we grant you the right to install and run one instance of the software on your device, for use by one person at a time, so long as you comply with all the terms of this agreement. Updating or upgrading from non-genuine software with software from Zerostic or authorized sources does not make your original version or the updated/upgraded version genuine, and in that situation, you do not have a license to use the software.\n<b>\n2) Privacy Consent and Use of Data</b>\n\nYour privacy is important to us. Some of the software features send or receive information when using those features. Many of these features can be switched off in the user interface, or you can choose not to use them. By accepting this agreement and using the software you agree that Zerostic may collect and use the information as described in the Zerostic privacy policy, and as may be described in the user interface associated with the software features.\n\n<b>3) Network and Internet Usage</b>\n\nSome features of the software and services accessed through the software may require your device to access the Internet. Your access and usage (including charges) may be subject to the terms of your cellular or internet provider agreement.\n\n<b>Just few more things\n\nZerostic has the right to update its terms of service and privacy policy in future if Zerostic updates its ToS or Privacy Policy it will inform you in advance and its upon you whether you want to continue using our software’s or services. Zerostic can delete your data or information as well as your account stored in our systems if you do not accept our terms in future, without accepting the terms of service or privacy policy use of any software’s or service provided by Zerostic will be considered illegal.</b>\n\n"</string>
    <string name="privacy">"<b>Privacy Policy</b>\n\nWhen you use our software’s and services, we collect some information from you to provide you the best of features we can. This is a big responsibility and we do understand this, also we do our best to protect your information, because we at Zerostic believe that <b>your privacy matters.</b>\n\n<b>Information that we collect.</b>\n\nWe collect information based on the software or service you use. All your information is saved on our server except some of your confidential information such as account details. <b>Zerostic never stores your account details.</b>\n\nYou may access some of our services by signing up for a Zerostic Account and providing us with some personal information (typically your name, email address, and a password). This account information is used to authenticate you when you access Zerostic services and protect your account from unauthorized access by others. You can edit or delete your account at any time by contacting us.\n\n<b>Information that we share.</b>\n\nInformation that we share depends on the software and services you are using keeping in mind that your data is safe. Zerostic may share required/relevant information about you with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. However, we only divulge aggregate information about our users and will not share personally identifiable information with any third party without your express consent.\n\n<b>We reserve the right at our discretion to make changes to this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes.</b>\n\n"</string>
    <string name="refund">"<b>Refund Policy\n\nZerostic Refund Policy</b>\n\nSome content made available on the application can be availed only by registered Users who have registered under a subscription model (Paid User). You may need to register yourself on the website in future to avail these services on a subscription model (Subscription).\n\nTo become a Paid User, you may be required to provide certain personal information to Zerostic and may be required to make payments (\"Subscription Fee\") as per the applicable membership plan through a debit card, credit card, internet banking or through, e- prepaid wallet or other payment method accepted by Zerostic (\"Payment Method(s)\") that You opted for during registration. Zerostic will be using third party payment gateways to process and facilitate the payment of your Subscription Fee to Zerostic. On successful registration to the Subscription, Zerostic will notify you of the same. Zerostic may offer different kinds of Subscription plans, each of these subscription plans will be subject to different limitations and restrictions and the cost of each of these subscription plans may vary.\n\nZerostic shall have the discretion to make certain content that is a part of the subscription available to you on more than one end user compatible system concurrently.\n\n<b>Free Trial</b>\n\nSome of the Subscription plans may start with a free trial. The free trial period may last for a period of one month or such other term as may be determined by Zerostic. Your eligibility for a free trial including the time for such free trial and the Content available to be viewed during free trial period is at the discretion of Zerostic and such free trial can be modified, suspended, or terminated by Zerostic at any point of time. In case your existing plan has expired Zerostic will automatically start your Free Plan which consists of limited features in the software. During the Free Plan (not to be confused with FREE TRIAL) you must watch one ad per day which will allow you to use the application with the limitations. In case you opt not to watch the ad then automatically all the features will stop working and you will not be able to use the application, but the basic features (as decided by Zerostic) will be still working. During the Free Plan, ads do not add up, so if you do not want to use the application any day you do not need to watch the ad either. It is up to you if you want to upgrade from a Free Plan to a subscription.\n\n<b>Subscription</b>\n\nBy providing your selected Payment Method, you authorize Zerostic (through its third-party payment gateway) to charge the applicable card or method for the Fee and you represent and warrant that you are the cardholder or account holder. In respect of a Subscription plan, you authorize Zerostic (through its third-party payment gateway) to charge your selected Payment Method for the Fees associated with your Subscription plan for monthly basis (for monthly plans) or yearly basis (for yearly plans) unless you provide notice that you no longer wish to receive the Subscription plan, or the Subscription plan is terminated in accordance with the Terms of Zerostic. If Payment Method is rejected by your card issuer or account provider, Zerostic will have no obligation to fulfil your order. Zerostic will automatically start billing as per Your selected Payment Method for the Subscription plan elected by You at the time of registration through the third-party payment gateway at the end of the free trial period, if applicable unless you cancel the Subscription before the end of the free trial period. The cancellation of the Subscription can be done through the \"Payment\" section in the settings of the application. It may take a few days for your payment made to Zerostic to be reflected in your \"Profile\" section. Zerostic offers two plans for INDIA and other countries they are:\n\n<b>INDIA (The amount will be charged in INR)</b>\n\n1st Plan includes services for 30 days that is the monthly subscription which starts from the day of the payment confirmation from the third-party payment gateways.\n\n2nd Plan includes services for 365 days that is the yearly subscription which starts from the day of the payment confirmation from the third-party payment gateways.\n\n<b>Other Countries (The amount will be charged in USD)</b>\n\n1st Plan includes services for 90 days that is the Quarterly subscription which starts from the day of the payment confirmation from the third-party payment gateways.\n\n2nd Plan includes services for 365 days that is the yearly subscription which starts from the day of the payment confirmation from the third-party payment gateways.\n\nAny of the Plans stated above (including plans for INDIA and other countries) cannot be cancelled after its activation. Zerostic will never activate any of the plans without your confirmation even if you have opted for recurring subscription.\n\n<b>The Subscription Fees billed are non-refundable irrespective of whether the Subscription have been availed by you or not. Any changes in the Subscription Plan opted by you is effective only after the expiry of the current subscription period for which you have already been billed. No amount will be refunded in any case, but you can contact Zerostic though. Zerostic has the right to change its refund policy in future.</b>\n\n"</string>
    <string name="ads">Watch Ad</string>
    <string name="freePlanAd">Hey, you are on a free plan and you need to watch one ad per day, watch this short ad and enjoy your one day of Good Morning for free.</string>
    <string name="defaultText">Default</string>
    <string name="maths">Maths</string>
    <string name="shake">Shake</string>
    <string name="walk">Walk</string>
    <string name="barCode">Bar Code</string>
    <string name="pattern">Pattern</string>
    <string name="text">Text</string>
    <string name="challengeMode">Challenge Mode</string>
    <string name="methodPageHeading">How do you want to turn it off?</string>
    <string name="recommeded">recommended</string>
    <string name="danger">danger</string>
    <string name="why_i_need_to_signIn">Why I need to Sign In?</string>
    <string name="why_user_needs_to_signIn">We need to know users payment status to provide you more of Zerostic. That\'s why we require you to sign in. But don\'t worry your data is safe with us.</string>
    <string name="why_ads">Why Ads?</string>
    <string name="why_user_has_to_watch_ads">We want to provide more features but unfortunately it\'s not possible under <b>Free Plan</b> as we also have to pay our expenses so for users in <b>Free Plan</b> we ask them to watch one ad per day so that it benefits both of us.</string>
    <string name="contact_zerostic">How to contact Zerostic?</string>
    <string name="how_to_contact">You can contact us at our email ID <b>support@zerostic.com</b> and we are working on more areas where you can contact Zerostic.</string>
    <string name="invite">Invite friends</string>
    <string name="whatsapp_logo">WhatsApp Logo</string>
    <string name="share_on_whatsapp">Share on WhatsApp</string>
    <string name="share_on_instagram">Share on Instagram</string>
    <string name="share_on_messenger">Share on Messenger</string>
    <string name="free_trial_activated">Free Trial Activated</string>
    <string name="verification_button">Verification Button</string>
    <string name="message_type">Message Type</string>
    <string name="type_your_message_here">Type your message here</string>
    <string name="send_button">Send Button</string>
    <string name="faqs">FAQs</string>
    <string name="expand_button">Expand</string>
    <string name="message_us">Message Us</string>
    <string name="update_available">Update Available</string>
    <string name="not_now">Not Now</string>
    <string name="write_the_above_text_here">Write the above text here...</string>
    <string name="source_openweathermap">Source: OpenWeatherMap</string>
    <string name="correct_or_incorrect">Correct or Incorrect</string>
    <string name="life_time_membership">Life-Time Membership</string>
    <string name="nextpage">nextPage</string>
    <string name="decline">DECLINE</string>
    <string name="accept">ACCEPT</string>
    <string name="deletetrackerdata">deleteTrackerData</string>
    <string name="msg_token_fmt">value</string>
    <string name="alarm_tone_heading">Change your alarm tone here</string>
    <string name="to_play">to play</string>
    <string name="why_should_i_turn_off_bluetooth_after_scheduling_the_alarm">Why should I turn off bluetooth after scheduling the alarm?</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_problem">We recommend you to turn of bluetooth so that no audio device can get connected to your mobile until we fire the alarm.</string>
    <string name="upload_button">upload button</string>
    <string name="remove_image">remove image</string>
    <string name="_2_minutes">2 Minutes</string>
    <string name="_3_minutes">3 Minutes</string>
    <string name="_4_minutes">4 Minutes</string>
    <string name="_5_minutes">5 Minutes</string>
    <string name="_6_minutes">6 Minutes</string>
    <string name="_7_minutes">7 Minutes</string>
    <string name="_8_minutes">8 Minutes</string>
    <string name="_9_minutes">9 Minutes</string>
    <string name="_10_minutes">10 Minutes</string>
    <string name="remove_snooze">Remove Snooze</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="delete_button">delete button</string>
    <string name="good_morning_logo">Good Morning Logo</string>
    <string name="suggestion">Suggestion</string>
    <string name="query">Query</string>
    <string name="complaint">Complaint</string>
    <string name="have_a_coupon_code">Have a coupon code?</string>
    <string name="redeem">Redeem</string>
    <string name="wake_up_check">Wake Up Check</string>
    <string name="repeat_off"><![CDATA[Repeat -> Off]]></string>
    <string name="alarm">Alarm</string>
    <string name="challenge_mode">Challenge Mode</string>
    <string name="_00_00">00:00</string>
    <string name="sun">Sun</string>
    <string name="mon">Mon</string>
    <string name="tue">Tue</string>
    <string name="wed">Wed</string>
    <string name="thu">Thu</string>
    <string name="fri">Fri</string>
    <string name="sat">Sat</string>
    <string name="remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="continue_without_login">Continue without login</string>
    <string name="nexticon">nextIcon</string>
    <string name="anonymously">Anonymously</string>
    <string name="using_emailid">Using EmailID</string>
    <string name="missing_data_message">Hey, we found that you have not provided us some basic information. Please select on how you signed in and provide us with these details as it is required for the application to function properly.</string>
    <string name="missing_settings">Default Settings Missing</string>
    <string name="missing_settings_message">Hey, your default settings are missing. Please set it from the button below.</string>
    <string name="signOut">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="some_basic_details">Some basic details</string>
    <string name="registering_user">Creating your account</string>
    <string name="alarm_title">Alarm Title :</string>
    <string name="alarm_title_text">Alarm</string>
    <string name="method">Method :</string>
    <string name="alarm_tone">Alarm Tone :</string>
    <string name="snooze_time">Snooze Time :</string>
    <string name="schedule_alarm">Schedule Alarm</string>
    <string name="clear_icon">Clear Icon</string>
    <string name="clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="update_available_message">A new version of Good Morning is available. Please update to enjoy the latest features.</string>
    <string name="notification_permission_heading">Notification Permission</string>
    <string name="notification_permission_message">Good Morning needs notification permission to send you alarm notifications. Please enable it.</string>
    <string name="weather_icon">Weather Icon</string>
    <string name="enter_your_location">Enter your location</string>
    <string name="get_weather">Get Weather</string>
    <string name="settings_button">Settings Button</string>
    <string name="preview_button">Preview Button</string>
    <string name="alphabetic_pattern">Alphabetic Pattern</string>
    <string name="numeric_pattern">Numeric Pattern</string>
    <string name="_6_patterns">6 Patterns</string>
    <string name="_8_patterns">8 Patterns</string>
    <string name="_10_patterns">10 Patterns</string>
    <string name="edit_alarm_title">Edit Alarm Title</string>
    <string name="rescan_code">Rescan Code</string>
    <string name="add_alarm">Add Alarm</string>
    <string name="todo">Todo</string>
</resources>
